McConnell, John W., Papers /3052
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Great Northern Paper Co., Millinocket, Maine vs. International Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 658 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Great Northern Paper Company vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 658, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  6/17/1978
- Great Northern Paper Co. vs. Office and Professional Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 192 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  no date on award
- Great Northern Paper Co. vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, Local lodge 362, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  11/4/1972
- Great Northern Paper Co vs. United Paper workers International Union, Local 12, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  12/10/1974
- Great Northern Paper Co. vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 362, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  9/28/1971
- Great Northern Paper Co vs. United Paper workers International Union, Local 12, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  3/3/1976
- Great Northern Paper Co vs. United Paper workers International Union, Local 12, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  6/14/1977
- Great Northern Paper Co. Pinkham member Division, vs. United Paper workers International Union, Local 1310 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Great Northern Paper Co. vs. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, Local69, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  5/8/1978
- Great Northern Paper Co vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 24, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  12/10/1976
- Great Northern Paper Co, Woodlands Operations vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 1977, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  9/18/1978
- Great Scott Food Markets Trading as Big G Discount Foods vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Bitcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  4/19/1970
- Greece Central School District vs. Greece Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  11/22/1976
- Greenwich, Connecticut Board of Education vs. Greenwich Education Association, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Griffiss Air Force Base, Rome, New York vs. American Federation of Government Employees, Local 2612, AFL-CIO, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  3/15/1975
- Griffiss Air Force Base, Department of the Air Force, Rome, New York vs. American Federation of Government Employees, Local 2612, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Grinnell Corporation, Cranston, R.I vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4756, AFL-CIO (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Gundry, Inc. A.R., Rochester, New York vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers, Local 8-709, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  5/22/1972
- Hamburg Central School District vs. Hamburg Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  7/30/1975
- Handy and Harman vs. United Steelworkers of America, District No. 1 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  grievance settled without arbitration, no award
- Hardwick, Vermont, Board of School Directors vs. Hardwick Elementary Teachers Association, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  8/21/1973
- Harwood Union High School, Moretown, Vermont, Board of School Directors vs. Harwood Union Teachers Association, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  12/5/1973
- Harpursville Central School District vs. Harpursville Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  10/8/1976
- Hartford Board of Education, Hartford, Connecticut vs. Hartford Federation of Teachers, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  2/28/1975
- Hartford School District, Hartford, Vermont vs. Hartford Teachers Association (Box 14, Folder 9)
  no date on fact finding report
- Heinrich Motors, Inc. Rochester, New York vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers, Local 1034, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  award 3/20/78, clarification of award 5/18/78
- Heist Corp, C.H, Tonawanda, NY vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Work house men and Helpers of America, Teamsters Local 375, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  10/13/1976
- Herkimer Central School District, Board of Education vs. Herkimer Faculty Association, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  6/24/1977
- Hilliard Corporation, Elmira NY vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 311, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  11/3/1976
- Hinsdale Products Co, Inc., Hinsdale, NH vs. United Paperworkers Union, Local 483, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  8/1/1979
- Hooker Chemicals and Plastics Corporation, Niagara Falls, NY vs. Niagara Hooker Employees Union, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  2/28/1976
- Hooker Chemical Corporation., The Durey Plastics Division vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local Lodge 2112, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  8/23/1971
- Hoover Ball and Bearing Company, Springfield, MA, Uniloy-Springfield Division vs. D.A.L.U. Local 24 850 of the AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Hornell, NY, City of vs. Hornell Police Association, McConnell mediation, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  on 4/1/72-3/31/74 contract negotiations and was appointed in a letter dated 8/22/72
- Horseheads Central School District vs. Horseheads Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  6/19/1976
- Horseheads Central School District vs. Horseheads Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  11/30/1976
- Horseheads Central School District vs. Horseheads Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  8/9/1974
- Horseheads, NY, Board of Education vs. Horseheads Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  6/3/1974
- Horseheads Central School District vs. Horseheads Teachers Association, Local 2739, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  9/30/1975
- Hotel Utica vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders, Local Union 136 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  dispute settled voluntarily after an adjourned hearing, no award
- Howe Richardson Scale Co, Rutland, Vermont vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 1590, AFL-CIO, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  10/24/1973
- Hudson Valley Community College, Troy, NY vs. Hudson Valley Community College Faculty Association, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  12/14/1978
- ITT Continental Baking Co., Natik, MA vs. Bakery and Confectionary Workers Local 348 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  no award in this FF, see following file folder
- ITT Continental Baking Co., Natik, MA vs. Bakery and Confectionary Workers Local 348, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  11/17/1976
- ITT Continental Baking Co, Buffalo, NY vs. Bakery Drivers Union, Local 264 of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  11/5/1976
- ITT Royal Electric Division, Pawtucket, Rhode Island vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1196, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  6/19/1979
- Imperial Paper and Color Corp, vs. United Mine Workers of America, District 50, Local 12962, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  11/7/1955
- International Harvester Co, Manchester, NH vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers, Local Union 633, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  4/16/1972
- Ithaca, NY, City of vs. Police Benevolent Association, fact finding report (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Johns-Mauville Production Corp, Nashua NH, vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 13012, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  12/17/1973
- Johnston, RI, the School Committee vs. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1491, Council 70, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  3/8/1974
- Julliard & Co, Incorporated, A.D. Atlantic Mills, Stottnele, NY vs. Textile Workers Union of ?, Columbia County, Bd. Local 96, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  4/23/1950
- Kellogg Brush Manufacturing Co. vs. Directly Affiliated Cabin Union, AFL-CIO Local 24 or 25, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  10/10/1977
- Kendall Company, Fiber Products Division vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local 642, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  8/5/1974
- Leesona Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 1605, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  11/25/1969
- Iceland and Gray Union High School, Board of Directors vs. Windham Central District Teachers Association, Mediation (Box 16, Folder 4)
  no award contained in file
- Lemoille Union High School, School Directors of vs. Lemoille Union High School Teachers Association (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Lexington, Massachusetts, Town of, the School Committee vs. Lexington Education Association, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  8/27/1973
- Lexington, Massachusetts, Town of, the School Committee vs. Lexington Education Association (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Lexington School committee vs. Lexington Teachers Association, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  1/20/1978
- Lincoln Pulp and Paper Co vs. United Paper workers International Union, Local 396, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  7/18/1978
- Lincoln Pulp and Paper Co vs. United Paper workers International Union, Local 396 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  no award in file
- Lisbon, Maine, School Committee vs. Lisbon Education Association, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  3/28/1973
- Liverpool Central School district vs. United Liverpool Faculty Association, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  7/25/1977
- Long Island Railroad vs. The Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Locals 517 and 1090, Board of Inquiry, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  investigation and final report, August 1960
- Longmeadow School Committee Negotiation Committee vs. Longmeadow Education Association (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Longmeadow School Committee vs. Longmeadow Education Association, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  12/22/1976
- Lowell Rendering Company vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers Workmen, District Union Local 2 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  no award, matter settled by parties before hearing
- Lowell Rendering Company vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers Workmen, District Union Local 2 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Lowell Rendering Company vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers Workmen, District Union Local 2, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  2/8/1971
- Ludlow Corporation vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local 1711, McConnell as chairman (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Ludlow Corporation (Ware Plant) vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 708, no date (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Mohopac Central School District vs. Mohopac Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  2/2/1976
- Marlborough, Massachusetts., City of vs. Marlborough Firefighters Association, Local 1714, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  9/30/1977
- Marx Company, Inc. of PA, Louis (Erie Plant) vs. Toymakers Lodge 1520, International Association of Machinists, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  8/13/1962
- McElwain Company (Manchester Plant), J.F. vs. New Hampshire Shoe Workers Union, Manchester, McConnell as chairman (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Mead Containers vs. Pulp, Sulphite, and Papermill Workers, Local 431 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  matter settled by parties
- Medford, MA, City of vs. United City, County and State Employees Union, Local 492, Building Services Employees International Union, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  6/2/1970
- Melrose, MA, Town of vs. Melrose Education Association (Box 17, Folder 8)
  no award found in folder
- Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, NYC vs. Insurance Workers International Union, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  2/6/1970
- Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, NYC vs. Insurance Workers International Union (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Milton Cooperative Dairy, Milton, Vermont vs. New England Joint Board, Local 479, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Milton District School Board vs. Milton Education Association (Box 17, Folder 12)
  mediation
- Mobil Oil Corp (New England Marketing Division.) vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-766, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  12/30/1971
- Mobil Oil Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-766, 1977-1979 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  9/12/77 (award) and response (denial) to Union's request for reopening the case 9/28/79
- Monroe Community College vs. Monroe Community College Faculty Association (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Monroe, NY, County of vs. Civil Service Employees Association, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  6/16/1977
- Monsanto Company, Springfield Plant vs. Monsanto Industrial Union, International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 288, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  8/15/1973
- Montachusett Regional Vocational Technical School Committee vs. Montachusett Regional Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  11/29/1975
- Morrison-Krudsen Company, Incorporated & Steward and William, Incorporated vs. Truck Drivers Local No. 340, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Portlan, Maine (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Morse Chain Company, Ithaca, NY vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace workers, Local Lodge 1607, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  2/2/1972
- Morse Chain Company, Ithaca, NY vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace workers, Local Lodge 1607, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  11/29/1971
- Morse Chain Company, Ithaca, NY vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace workers, Local Lodge 1607, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  10/17/72, (Division of Borg Warren)
- Morse Chain Company, Ithaca, NY vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace workers, Local Lodge 1607, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  6/26/1972
- Morse Chain Company, Ithaca, NY vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace workers, Local Lodge 1607, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  11/6/1972
- Morton Salt Co, Penn Yan, NY vs., International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2364 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  no award, grievance settled voluntarily by parties
- Nashua Board of Education vs. The Nashua Teachers Union, Local 1044, American Federation of Teachers, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  3/17/1972
- National Gypsum Co., Clarence Center, NY vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-247 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Naval Air Station, Quon set Point, RI vs. National Association of Government Employees, Local R.I-7 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Nestle Co, Inc, Fulton, NY vs. United Laboratory Workers Union, Local 1975 of Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  6/13/1976
- Nestle Co, Inc, Fulton, NY vs. United Laboratory Workers Union, Local 1975 of Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  3/31/1976
- New Bedford Gas and Edison Light Co. vs. Brotherhood of Utility Workers of New England, Local 333, McConnell as chairman (Box 18, Folder 9)
- New Boston Garden Corporation vs. Service Employees International Union, Local 254, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  9/13/1946
- New Boston Garden Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1499, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  5/11/1979
- New Hartford Central School District vs. New Hartford Teachers Association, expedited arbitration, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  6/1/1974
- New Haven, Connecticut, Board of Education vs. Robert W. Duda, guidance counselor, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  4/18/1975
- New York Air Brake Co, Watertown, NY vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 761, District 137, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  5/15/1978
- New York Air Brake Co, Watertown, NY vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 761, District 137 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- New York, State of, office of Drug Abuse Services vs. Security and Law Enforcement Employees, Council 82, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  1/30/1976
- New York, State University of, at Binghamton vs. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Council 82 and civil Service Employees Association, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- New York, State of, office of Parks and Recreation vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Workers, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  10/6/1975
- New York, State of vs. AFSCME, Council 82, state presentation (Box 19, Folder 4)
- New York, State of vs. AFSCME, Council 82, state exhibit (Box 19, Folder 5)
- New York, State of vs. AFSCME, Council 82, transcript (Box 19, Folder 6)
- New York, State of vs. AFSCME, Council 82, transcript (Box 19, Folder 7)
- New York, State of vs. AFSCME, Council 82, Findings and Recommendations of Fact Finding Panel, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  5/20/71, 5 volumes of transcripts for above
- NY, State of vs. Security Unit Employees Council 82, AFSCME (Box 19, Folder 9)
  no award in folder, house exhibit
- NY, State of vs. Security Unit Employees Council 82, AFSCME (Box 19, Folder 10)
  no award in folder, miscellaneous exhibit
- NY, State of, Dept. of Mental Hygiene, Newark, Development Center vs. Civil Service Employees Association, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  4/1/1976
- NY, State of, Department of Mental Hygiene, Gouarda Psychiatric Center vs. CSEA, Institutional Services Unit, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  11/15/1975
- NY, State of, Mental Hygiene Facility, Kingsboro Psychiatric Center vs. CSEA, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  4/5/1976
- New York, State of, Department of Mental Hygiene, Rochester Psychiatric Center vs. CSEA, Local 420, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  8/10/1976
- New York, State of, Department of Mental Hygiene, Letchworth Village Development Center, vs. CSEA (Box 19, Folder 15)
- New York, State of, Department of Mental Hygiene vs. CSEA, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  8/5/1975
- New York, State of, Department of Correctional Services vs. CSEA, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  8/12/1975
- New York, State of, Department of Mental Hygiene, Hudson River Psychiatric Center vs. CSEA (Box 19, Folder 18)
  no award found in file folder
- New York, State of, Department of Mental Hygiene, Willowbrook Development Centers vs. CSEA (Box 19, Folder 19)
- New York, State of, Department of Mental Hygiene, Newark Developmental Centers vs. CSEA (Box 20, Folder 1)
  no award found in file
- New York, State of, Department of Mental Hygiene vs. CSEA (Box 20, Folder 2)
- New York, State of, Department of Mental Hygiene, Willowbrook Developmental Center vs. CSEA (Box 20, Folder 3)
- New York, State of, Department of Mental Hygiene, Wassaic Development Center vs. CSEA, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  10/15/76, the rest of box 20 contains several binders of miscellaneous exhibits and 6 volumes of transcripts re New York, State of vs. CSEA, dated 4/5,6,8,12,13,16/75
- New York, State of vs. CSEA, matter of fact-finding, McConnell on panel appointed by the Public Employee Relations Board, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  4/25/75 opinion and recommendation
- New York, State of, Department of Mental Hygiene, Newark Development Center vs. CSEA, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  6/26/78 award, 8/3/78 reaffirmation of the award denying a modification request made by the State
- New York, State of, Department of Mental Hygiene, Syracuse Development Center vs. CSEA, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  1/12/77, folder 3: New York State, Department of Mental Hygiene, St. Lawrence Psych Center, no date on rough copy of award
- New York, State of, Department of Social Services vs. CSEA, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corp vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (Box 21, Folder 5)
  no award found in folder file
- New York State United Teachers vs. Professional Staff Organization of NYSUT, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  3/15/1978
- New York Telephone Co (Utica Area) vs. Communication Workers of America, Dist Ore, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  10/6/1978
- Newfare Central School Dist vs. Newfare Teachers Association, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  6/13/1979
- Newington, Connecticut, Board of Education vs. Newington Teachers Association, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  7/12/1978
- Newport, Rhode Island, School Committee vs. Teachers Association of Newport (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Newport, Rhode Island, School Committee vs. Teachers Association of Newport, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  5/22/1973
- Newport, Rhode Island, City of vs. AFSCME, AFL-CIO, Local 911 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  no award found in ff
- Newport, Rhode Island, School Department vs. Teachers Association of Newport, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Newton, MA, City of vs. Newton Police Association, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  2/23/1977
- Newton Falls Paper Co, NF, NY vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 1154, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  11/22/1974
- Newton Falls Paper Co, NF, NY vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 1154, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  5/20/1975
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corp, Amsterdam, NY vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1371, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  9/13/1978
- Orleans-Essex North Supervisory Union, Boards of School Directors of the vs. the North County Education Association, Fact finders report, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  5/19/1974
- North Harem, Connecticut, Board of Education vs. Grievant, Mrs. Annie M. Haynes and Mrs. Hanlyn Horn, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  2/6/1978
- North Smithfield, R.I, School Committee vs. N. Smithfield Teachers Association, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  6/9/1972
- No. Smithfield, R.I School Committee vs. Smithfield Teachers Association, McConnell on Board of Arbitration (Box 22, Folder 1)
  no date on rough draft of award
- North Syracuse School District vs. CSEA, Transportation United, No. Syracuse, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  2/12/1973
- No. Syracuse School District vs. No. Syracuse Educational Association, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  2/5/1974
- No. Syracuse Central School District vs. No. Syracuse Education Association, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  9/7/1978
- Northrup Corp Precision Production Dept., Norwood, MA vs. International Union United Automobiles, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1596 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Northrup Corp Precision Production Dept., Norwood, MA vs. International Union United Automobiles, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1596, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  11/2/1973
- Northrup Corp Precision Production Dept., Norwood, MA vs. International Union United Automobiles, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1596, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  9/18/1973
- Norwich, Connecticut, Board of Education vs. Norwich Teachers League, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  4/13/1976
- Owens-Illinois, Inc, Division vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 570, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  1/6/1975
- Olin Corp., New Haven, Connecticut vs. Lodge 609 of International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  11/9/1971
- Onondaga Central School District vs. Onondaga Central School District Non-Instructional Employees Association, mediators report (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Onondaga Community College vs. Onondaga Community College Federation of Teachers, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  award 12/7/76, response to request for modification of the award 1/18/77
- Oswego City School District vs. Oswego Classroom Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  5/20/1976
- Oxford Paper Co., Ethyl Corp, Rumford, Maine vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 900, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Oxford Paper Co., Ethyl Corp, Rumford, Maine vs. United Paper workers International Union, Local 900, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  3/31/1970
- Oxford Paper Co., Ethyl Corp, Rumford, Maine vs. United Paper workers International Union, Local 900, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  1/24/1976
- Palmer School Committee, Palmer MA vs. Palmer Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  4/4/1975
- Payne Jones, Inc. vs. Lowville, NY vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 1988, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  5/11/1976
- Peerless Press Metals Corp, Watertown, MA vs. International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers, Local 209, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  10/13/1973
- Peerless Press Metals Corp, Watertown, MA vs. International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers, Local 209 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  no award, matter withdrawn from arbitration
- Pettibone Corp, Rome NY vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local Lodge 1512, District Lodge 157, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  11/9/1974